<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ProcessDefinition configVersion="3.0.0" processVersion="1.0.0" xmlns="http://www.deegree.org/processes/java"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.deegree.org/processes/java http://schemas.deegree.org/processes/java/3.0.0/java.xsd">
	<Identifier>MarkItemsReviewed</Identifier>
	<JavaClass>hoot.services.controllers.wps.MarkItemsReviewedProcesslet</JavaClass>
  <Title>Mark Items Reviewed Service</Title>
  <Abstract><![CDATA[
  <DESCRIPTION>After editing reviewable items, this method is called to mark the items as having been reviewed. The inputs to the service method are either a JSON structure which describes the status of the review for each reviewed item, or when setting a boolean true to mark all items as reviewed the structure is not required. Also optionally for convenience sake, a OSM XML changeset may be included in the request to upload a changeset in the same call which marks data as reviewed. If a changeset is uploaded, the service automatically creates and closes the changeset that stores the uploaded data. The response from the server contains the outcome of the changeset upload and the changeset ID created (if a changeset was uploaded) as well as the number of submitted items that were actually marked as reviewed. Clients can compare this number to the number of items sent for review, and if they are not equal, further troubleshooting should occur.
  For each item in the reviewed items JSON, the service will:

      mark the reviewable item as reviewed, so that it will not be returned for review again
      append the UUID of the item the reviewed item was reviewed against to its "uuid" OSM tag
      remove the UUID of the item reviewed against from the "hoot:review:uuid" OSM tag of the reviewed item
      remove all OSM review tags from the reviewed item, if it no longer contains items to be reviewed against

  The caller is responsible for doing the following things, as the service will not automatically do them:

  Adding the "changeset" XML attribute to the elements in the XML changeset being uploaded, as is required by the standard OSM changeset upload service. The changeset ID attribute value may either be blank or populated with a number, however, the changeset ID will be overwritten with the ID of the changeset created by the service method execution.
</DESCRIPTION>
  <EXAMPLE>
  <URL>http://localhost:8080/hoot-services/ogc/MarkItemsReviewed</URL>
  <REQUEST_TYPE>POST</REQUEST_TYPE>
  <INPUT></INPUT>
   <OUTPUT></OUTPUT>
   </EXAMPLE>
  ]]></Abstract>
	<InputParameters>
		<LiteralInput minOccurs="1" maxOccurs="1">
      <Identifier>mapId</Identifier>
      <Title>Map ID</Title>
      <Abstract>string; required; ID string or unique name of the map associated with the reviewable conflated data</Abstract>
      <Metadata href="http://schemas.mrgeo.org/wps/0.1.0/#Icon" about="formulaIcon"/>
      <DataType reference="http://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#string">string</DataType>
    </LiteralInput>
    <LiteralInput minOccurs="0" maxOccurs="1">
      <Identifier>markAll</Identifier>
      <Title>Mark All</Title>
      <Abstract>boolean; optional; defaults to false; indicates whether all items belonging to the map should be marked as reviewed</Abstract>
      <Metadata href="http://schemas.mrgeo.org/wps/0.1.0/#Icon" about="formulaIcon"/>
      <DataType reference="http://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#boolean">boolean</DataType>
      <DefaultValue>false</DefaultValue>
    </LiteralInput>
    <LiteralInput minOccurs="0" maxOccurs="1">
      <Identifier>reviewedItems</Identifier>
      <Title>Reviewed Items</Title>
      <Abstract>JSON object; required if markAll is set to false; optional otherwise; lists the items which should be marked as reviewed</Abstract>
      <Metadata href="http://schemas.mrgeo.org/wps/0.1.0/#Icon" about="formulaIcon"/>
      <DataType reference="http://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#string">string</DataType>
    </LiteralInput>
    <LiteralInput minOccurs="0" maxOccurs="1">
      <Identifier>reviewedItemsChangeset</Identifier>
      <Title>Reviewed Items Changeset</Title>
      <Abstract>XML string; optional; OSM changeset XML</Abstract>
      <Metadata href="http://schemas.mrgeo.org/wps/0.1.0/#Icon" about="formulaIcon"/>
      <DataType reference="http://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#string">string</DataType>
    </LiteralInput>
	</InputParameters>
	<OutputParameters>
		<LiteralOutput>
			<Identifier>changesetUploadResponse</Identifier>
			<Title>Changeset Upload Response</Title>
			<Abstract></Abstract>
			<DataType reference="http://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#string">string</DataType>
		</LiteralOutput>
		<LiteralOutput>
      <Identifier>numItemsMarkedReviewed</Identifier>
      <Title>Number of Items Marked Reviewed</Title>
      <Abstract></Abstract>
      <DataType reference="http://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#integer">integer</DataType>
    </LiteralOutput>
    <LiteralOutput>
      <Identifier>changesetId</Identifier>
      <Title>Changeset ID</Title>
      <Abstract></Abstract>
      <DataType reference="http://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#integer">integer</DataType>
    </LiteralOutput>
	</OutputParameters>
</ProcessDefinition>
